siliconarmada.com 2017-06-22

# Silicon Armada - Tech Jobs for Tech People

Silicon Armada (referred to as: Website) is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. The following statement explains Website's commitment to managing your personal information and sets out how and when personal information is collected, held, used or disclosed. 

### Information About All Website Visitors

The Company authorizes You to view and access a single copy of the content available on or from Website (the "Web Site") solely for your personal, non-commercial use.

We gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas users visit most frequently and what services users access the most. We only use such data anonymously and in the aggregate. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you. We may share this information with our partners, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may understand how Website visitors use our site, and also create a better overall experience for you. We do not disclose information about your individual visits to Website to any outside parties, except when the law requires it.

### Information About You Specifically 

Website is a career site, we retain your personal information to assist in your career performance or management including finding or retaining work; or to facilitate other services to or by us. For example, when you sign up to use a service, enter into a contest, or purchase a product, we collect more specific personal information about you, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, credit card number, qualifications or career history. If you choose to do so we may also retain sensitive information about you such as information about your membership in a professional or trade association or trade union. We may also ask you for other information, such as information on your interests, your likes and dislikes regarding the site, the types of jobs you are interested in, etc., in an effort to deliver to you the best possible site experience. When you grant us your permission, we will communicate with you regularly with tips, advice and survey information on using the Website site to maximise your career development. Website also provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of these types of communications. If you choose to receive these types of communications at the time of registration, but later decide you no longer want to receive them, simply log in to your My Website account and edit your account profile. If you input your information on a co-branded registration page, such as that of a Website and partner company-sponsored contest, then your information will be collected, used and becomes the property of both Website and the partner co-sponsoring the contest. In that instance, Website is not responsible for the information that the partner company receives or how it is used. If you do not provide us with the information sought in the required fields Website may be limited in its ability to provide you with services.

### Disclosure of your information to other people

We may use other companies and third parties to perform services necessary to our operations. In the course of providing these services, those companies may have access to your personal information and such information may be transferred overseas. By contractual agreement, those companies must treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. However, we will not be liable (to the fullest extent permitted by law) for any damages that may result from the misuse of your personal information by these companies.

We give you the option of putting your resume in our database. There are two ways of doing this:

You can store your resume in our database, but not allow it to be searchable by potential employers or recruiters. Not allowing your resume to be searchable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to search it through our resume database product.

You can allow your resume to be searchable by employers, recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals who pay for access to our resume database and your resume. When you opt to make your resume searchable, you still have the choice to make your personal details confidential where all of your contact information and even your current place of employment can remain hidden. We use our best efforts to restrict access to our database only to those who have paid for access; these parties may retain a copy of your resume in their own files or databases. We take all reasonable steps to ensure parties other than those mentioned above will not, without our consent, gain access to this database. We endeavour to ensure those who gain access to your resume comply with the relevant privacy laws, however Website is not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of resumes by any third parties. We may share your information with our related companies. You may remove your resume from our searchable database at any time.

### Updating Account Information 

We wish to ensure your personal information is complete, accurate and up to date. Website allows you to change or correct your personal information at any time. To do so, simply log into your My Website account, and you will find options for editing the information you have submitted. 

### Online Security 

If you are buying a product from Website via the Web site, your personal details and credit card information are scrambled using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. Although we cannot guarantee encryption or the privacy of your personal details and credit card information, SSL makes it very difficult for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred. When we receive your order, it is kept encrypted until we're ready to process it. Website is committed to keeping the information you provide us with secure. We have security procedures in place to protect your personal information. 

### Website Database

The information you provide is stored on the Website database. To provide you with the highest quality service the Website database is located in the United States. When providing information you agree this may be transferred to our overseas database. 

### Cookies

Website respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users, account holders and content partners to do the same. The unauthorized reproduction, copying, distribution, modification, public display or public performance of copyrighted works constitutes infringement of the copyright owners rights. As a condition to your use of this Web Site, You agree not to use the Web Site or any other Website Site to infringe the intellectual property rights of others in any way. We will terminate the accounts of any account holders, and block access to our Web Site and/or the other Website Sites of any users, who are repeat infringers of the copyrights, or other intellectual property rights, of others. We reserve the right to take these actions at any time, in our sole discretion, with or without notice, and without any liability to the account holder who is terminated or to the user whose access is blocked.

To enhance your experience at Website, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie". Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for remembering user names and passwords and preferences, tracking click streams, and for load balancing. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalised site experience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our site.

Silicon Armada uses the AdWords and Remarketing Lists features of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers. Indeed and Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our Website. This means that vendors including Google will display Indeed promotional material on other sites you visit across the Internet.

You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers including AdWords and opt-out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Preferences Manager. To provide web site visitors more choice on how their data is collected by Google Analytics, Google has developed an Opt-out Browser add-on, which is available by visiting Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, to enable you to opt-out of Google's programs.

### Feedback

Website has areas on the site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes the property of Website. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the site

### Children

We do not collect any information on children. The site is strictly for the age group of 18 and above. 

The Company reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to pursue all of its legal remedies, Including but not limited to deletion of your postings from this Web Site and the other Website Sites and immediate termination of your registration with or ability to access this Web Site and the other Website Sites and/or any other service provided to You by the Company, upon any breach by You of these Terms and Conditions or if the Company is unable to verify or authenticate any information You submit to the Web Site.

### Privacy Commitment Changes 

We may make changes to our privacy commitment, we will post those changes on our Web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

Thank you for using Website. We're committed to providing you with the best tools and advice to help you get ahead in your career. We welcome your feedback and suggestions.
